<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.kmarkdownwebviewpart</id>
  <!--
    Appstream model currently does not support the idea of generic addons
    See https://github.com/ximion/appstream/issues/157
    As intermediate work-around some typical consumers are listed explicitely.
  -->
  <extends>org.kde.ark.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.kate.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.kdevelop.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.krusader.desktop</extends>
  <extends>org.kde.konqueror.desktop</extends>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.1+</project_license>
  <name>Markdown Viewer KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KPart del visor de Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KPart del visor de Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KPart pro prohlížení souborů Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Markdown-fremviseren KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Markdown-Betrachter-KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Προβολέας markdown του KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Markdown Viewer KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KPart del visor de Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Markdowni näitaja komponent</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Markdown-katseluosa</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Composant KDE de rendu Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KPart de visor de Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KPart di visualizzazione Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Markdown 뷰어 KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Markdown-viewer van KPart</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">KPart-framvisar for Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KPart Przeglądarki Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KPart de Visualização do Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KPart do visualizador de Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Компонент просмотра Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KPark prehliadač Markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Markdown KPart-visning</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Модуль перегляду даних markdown</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxMarkdown Viewer KPartxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Markdown 檢視器 KPart</name>
  <summary>Rendered display of Markdown files in KParts-using software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Mostra renderitzats els fitxers de Markdown en el programari que utilitza les KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mostra renderitzats els fitxers de Markdown en el programari que utilitza les KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Zpracované zobrazení Markdown v aplikacích využívajících KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Gengivet visning af Markdown-filer i KParts med software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Anzeige von Markdown-Dateien in Software, die KParts verwendet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Οθόνη αποτύπωσης αρχείων markdown σε λογισμικό που χρησιμοποιεί KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Rendered display of Markdown files in KParts-using software</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Pantalla de visualización de archivos Markdown en software que usa KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Markdowni renderdatud näitamine KPartsi kasutavas tarkvaras</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Näyttää Markdown-tiedostoja aseteltuna KParts-ohjelmissa</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Rendu à l'écran de fichiers Markdown dans les logiciels utilisant les composants KDE.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Visualización renderizada de ficheiros Markdown en software que usa KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione formattata di file Markdown in software che usano KPart</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">KParts를 사용하는 프로그램에서 Markdown 파일을 렌더링하여 표시합니다</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Toonbare weergave van Markdown-bestanden in software die KParts gebruikt</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Vising av Markdown-filer i program som støttar KPart</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Do renderowanego wyświetlania plików Markdown w oprogramowaniu używającym KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Apresentação desenhada dos ficheiros de Markdown nas aplicações baseadas no KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição renderizada de arquivos Markdown nos aplicativos que usam o KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Компонент просмотра файлов Markdown в отформатированном виде</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Renderované zobrazenie súborov Markdown v softvéri používajúcom KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Återgiven vy för Markdown-filer i programvara som använder KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Показ обробленого вмісту файлів markdown у програмному забезпеченні із підтримкою KParts</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxRendered display of Markdown files in KParts-using softwarexx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">在使用 KPart 的程式中繪製 Markdown 檔案的內容</summary>
  <description>
    <p>The Markdown Viewer KPart allows KParts-using software to display files in Markdown format in a rendered view.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">La KPart del visor de Markdown permet que el programari que utilitza les KParts, mostri els fitxers en format de Markdown en una vista renderitzada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">La KPart del visor de Markdown permet que el programari que utilitza les KParts, mostre els fitxers en format de Markdown en una vista renderitzada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Markdown-fremviseren KPart giver KParts mulighed for med software at vise filer i Markdown-format i en gengivet visning.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Die Markdown-Betrachter-Komponente befähigt Software, die KParts verwendet, zur Anzeige von Dateien im Markdown-Format.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Ο προβολέας markdown του KPart επιτρέπει σε λογισμικό που χρησιμοποιεί το KParts να εμφανίζει αρχεία σε μορφή markdown σε μια προβολή αποτύπωσης.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The Markdown Viewer KPart allows KParts-using software to display files in Markdown format in a rendered view.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El visor KPart de Markdown permite que el software que usa KParts muestre archivos en formato Markdown en un visor.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Markdowni näitaja komponent võimaldab KPartsi kasutaval tarkvaral näidata Markdowni vormingus faile renderdatud vaates..</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Markdown-katseluosa antaa KParts-sovelluksille mahdollisuuden näyttää Markdown-tiedostot asetellussa muodossa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le composant KDE de Markdown permet aux logiciels utilisant les composants KDE d'afficher des fichiers au format Markdown dans un rendu à l'écran.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O KPart de visor de Markdown permite ao software que usa KParts mostrar ficheiros en formato Markdown nunha vista renderizada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Visualizzatore KPart per Markdown permette al software che usa KPart di mostrare file in formato Markdown resi in un vista.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Markdown 뷰어 KPart를 사용하면 KParts를 사용하는 소프트웨어에서 Markdown 형식을 렌더링해서 볼 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De Markdownviewer van KPart stelt software die KPats gebruikt in staat bestanden in Markdown-formaat in een toonbare weergave.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">KPart-framvisaren for Markdown lèt deg visa filer Markdown-format i alle program som støttar KPart.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KPart przeglądarki Markdown umożliwia oprogramowaniu wykorzystującemu KParts wyświetlanie plików Markdown w widoku renderowanym.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KPart de Visualização do Markdown permite às aplicações baseadas no KParts mostrarem ficheiros de Markdown devidamente formatados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KPart do visualizador de Markdown permite que os aplicativos que usam o KParts mostrem arquivo Markdown devidamente formatados.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Компонент просмотра Markdown позволяет программам с поддержкой KParts показывать файлы Markdown в отформатированном виде.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">KPark prehliadača Markdown umožňuje softvéru používajúcemu KParts zobraziť súbory vo formáte Markdown v renderovanom pohľade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Markdown KPart-visning tillåter program som använder KParts att visa filer med Markdown-format i en återgiven vy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Модуль перегляду даних markdown надає змогу переглядати оброблений вміст файлів у форматі markdown у будь-якому програмному забезпеченні із підтримкою KParts.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe Markdown Viewer KPart allows KParts-using software to display files in Markdown format in a rendered view.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://cgit.kde.org/kmarkdownwebview.git/about/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kmarkdownwebview&amp;component=kpart</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kmarkdownwebview</url>
  <update_contact>kossebau_at_kde.org</update_contact>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kmarkdownwebview/kmarkdownwebview.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">text-markdown</icon>
</component>
